

Melur, Madurai, Tamilnadu, 625106, India

📥 Jul 2000

gopalakrishnan567890@gmail.com

+91 9952658175

https://gopalakrishnanportfolio.web.app/

Gopalakrishnan20

in Gopalakrishnan J

LeetCode

#### **PUBLICATIONS**

Multipurpose Linux Tool for Wi-Fi Based Attack, Information **Gathering and Web Vulnerability Scanning Automations** 

Springer Link

Part of the Lecture Notes in Networks and Systems book series (LNNS, volume 514)

https://bit.ly/3zAgoyX

#### **SKILLS**

Frontend Web Development Angular, HTML/CSS, TypeScript

## **Backend Development**

Springboot, Postman, Microservices, Hibernate

## **AWS Developer**

**Associate** 

Implementing highly available web application, SAM, Lambda, CI/CD, Security, Monitoring and troubleshooting

#### **LANGUAGES**

**Tamil English Fluent** Native

# Gopalakrishnan J

Associate Software Engineer | AWS Certified Developer

I am a creative Full Stack developer offering 1+ years of experience providing high-impact web solutions for diverse industry organizations. Skilled in designing, developing and testing multiple web-based applications incorporating a range of technologies.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

**Mphasis** 

(Jun 2022 - Present)

Associate Software Engineer

**Hack-X Security** 

(Jun 2021 - Oct 2021)

Security Researcher

- Done a research project on the topic Cryptography, Reported over 35+ Bug reports, Wrote a Blog, Build a Linux based tool using BASH Script.
- For details checkout the link below
- https://bit.ly/3FDbC7t

#### **EDUCATION**

Hindustan Institute of Technology and Science Bachelor of Technology, Information Technology Specialization in Cybersecurity

(Jul 2018 - May 2022) CGPA: 8.19/10

Velammal Bodhi Campus

Chellappan Vidya Mandir

(Jul 2017 - May 2018)

71%

(Jul 2015 - May 2016)

10th, CBSE

12th, CBSE

CGPA: 9.0/10

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

AWS Certified Developer -**Associate** 

(May **AWS Cloud Quest:** 2023) Security

(May 2023)

Amazon Web Service

Amazon Web Service

https://bit.ly/43ddFYN

https://bit.ly/3odKDcE

**AWS Cloud Quest: Solutions Architect** Amazon Web Service

2023)

(May

(Feb

2023)

**AWS Cloud Quest:** Serverless Developer Amazon Web Service

(Apr 2023)

https://bit.ly/428Sx5I

**AWS Cloud Quest: Cloud** 

https://bit.ly/3N6KnGk

**Cyber Security & Forensics** 

(Jun 2022)

**Practitioner** Amazon Web Services

http://bit.ly/3Jll7de

Graduate **IBM** 

https://bit.ly/3h6qd1g

INTERESTS	
Cybersecurity Enthusiast	Powerlifting
Basketball	Gymnastics

## **PROJECTS**

## **Hospital Management System**

Backend Development Lead

- Created a Database schema and assigned tasks to team members
- Developed REST APIs for the application with Business Logic
- Integrated the APIs with the Frontend
- https://github.com/Gopalakrishnan20/RLL-Hospital-Management-System.git

SpringBoot, Hibernate, Typescript, Postman, MySQL

Multipurpose Linux Tool for Wi-Fi Based Attack, Information Gathering and Web Vulnerability Scanning Automations (Dec 2021 - Apr 2022)

(Oct 2022 - Oct 2022)

Team Lead

- A Linux tool for Multiple functionalities like Information gathering, Wi-Fi attack, Web vulnerability scanning.
- Complete integration of various powerful automations.
- Published as a Conference Paper on Springer Link
- https://link.springer.com/chapter/10.1007/978-3-031-12413-6\_46
  OSINT, Bash, Python, Pentesting, WiJAMMER